gg.co.uk 2019-05-21

# Privacy Policy | gg.co.uk

**

This site uses cookies. By continuing to browse this site you are agree toour use of cookies.

×**

## What we use personal data for

We analyse information in our various systems and databases to help improve the way we run our business and our website according to user preferences, to provide a better service and user experience as well as to enhance our advertisements by providing information about the usage throughout the site.

We will make sure that we only process your personal data for these purposes:

  * you have provided your consent to us using the data in that way; or
  * our use of your personal data is necessary to support legitimate interests that we have as a business (for example, to improve our products, to offer you the use of bespoke services or to carry out analytics across our datasets), provided it is conducted at all times in a way that is proportionate, and that respects your privacy rights.

## Disclosure of your personal data

We work with third parties to manage our business and deliver services. These third parties may from time to time require access to your personal data:

  * Our analytics service providers such as Google, who process personal data for their own purposes as Data Controllers. Please refer to our Cookie Policy in order to identify how you may prevent access to your personal data by analytics providers.
  * We may transfer personal data in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we will disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;
  * if we, or substantially all of our assets, are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by us about our customers will be one of the transferred assets;
  * to protect the rights, property, or safety of us, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction; and
  * if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation or regulatory requirements, or otherwise for the prevention or detection of fraud or crime.

## Transfer to third countries outside the European Union/EEA

We may allow third parties, who may be located outside the European Union/EEA, access to your personal data.

We may also make other disclosures of your personal data overseas, for example if we receive a legal or regulatory request from a foreign law enforcement body.

We will always take steps to ensure that any international transfer of information is carefully managed to protect your rights and interests. Any requests for information we receive from law enforcement or regulators will be carefully checked before personal data is disclosed

You have the right to ask us for more information about the safeguards we have put in place as mentioned above.

## For how long we keep your personal data

We will retain your personal data for as long as is reasonably necessary for the valid purposes, or until you revoke your consent. In some circumstances we may retain your personal data for longer periods of time, for instance where we are required to do so in accordance with legal, regulator, tax or accounting requirements.

## Cookies

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile standard statistical reports on website activity.

To review the cookies we set please visit our Cookie Policy. For further information about cookies please visit [AboutCookies.org](https://aboutcookies.org/).

## External Links

Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.

## Your right to access

Most of the information we hold about you is available to view in the My Account section of our website. You may also request **access to your data** , **correction of any mistakes** in our files, **erasure of records** where no longer required, **restriction on the processing** of your data, **objection to the processing** of your data, **data portability** and various information in relation to the basis for **international transfers**. You may also exercise a right to complain to your **Supervisory Authority**. More information about each of these rights can be found by clicking on the relevant link or by referring to the table set out further below.

You have a number of rights in relation to your personal data.

### Right of Access

You can ask us to:

  * confirm whether we are processing your personal data;
  * give you a copy of that data;
  * provide you with other information about your personal data such as what data we have, what we use it for, who we disclose it to, whether we transfer it abroad and how we protect it, how long we keep it for, what rights you have, how you can make a complaint, where we got your data from and whether we have carried out any Automated Decision Making or Profiling, to the extent that information has not already been provided to you in this Policy.

### Right of Rectification

You can ask us to rectify inaccurate personal data.

We may seek to verify the accuracy of the data before rectifying it.

### Right of Erasure

You can ask us to erase your personal data, but only where:

  * it is no longer needed for the purposes for which it was collected; or
  * you have withdrawn your consent (where the data processing was based on consent); or
  * following a successful right to object (see ‘Objection’ below); or
  * it has been processed unlawfully; or
  * to comply with a legal obligation to which it is subject.

We are not required to comply with your request to erase your personal data if the processing of your personal data is necessary:

  * for compliance with a legal obligation; or
  * for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims;

There are certain other circumstances in which we are not required to comply with your erasure request, although these two are the most likely circumstances in which we would deny that request

### Right of Restriction

You can ask us to restrict (i.e. keep but not use) your personal data, but only where:

  * its accuracy is contested (see Rectification), to allow us to verify its accuracy; or
  * the processing is unlawful, but you do not want it erased; or
  * it is no longer needed for the purposes for which it was collected, but we still need it to establish, exercise or defend legal claims; or
  * you have exercised the right to object, and verification of overriding grounds is pending.

We can continue to use your personal data following a request for restriction, where:

  * we have your consent; or
  * to establish, exercise or defend legal claims; or
  * to protect the rights of another natural or legal person.

### Portability

You can ask us to provide your personal data to you in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format, or you can ask to have it ‘ported’ directly to another Data Controller, but in each case only where:

  * the processing is based on your consent or on the performance of a contract with you; and
  * the processing is carried out by automated means.

### Objection

You can object to any processing of your personal data which has our ‘legitimate interests’ as its legal basis, if you believe your fundamental rights and freedoms outweigh our legitimate interests.

Once you have objected, we have an opportunity to demonstrate that we have compelling legitimate interests which override your rights and freedoms.

### International Transfers

You can ask to obtain a copy of, or reference to, the safeguards under which your personal data is transferred outside of the European Economic Area.

We may redact data transfer agreements or related documents (i.e. obscure certain information contained within these documents) for reasons of commercial sensitivity.

### Supervisory Authority

You have a right to lodge a complaint with the responsible local supervisory authority about our processing of your personal data.

## Changes to our privacy policy

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on 26th April 2018

## How to contact us

Please contact us at help@gg.co.uk if you have any questions about our privacy policy or the information we hold about you.
